crystalidea.com 2019-05-05

# CrystalIDEA Privacy Agreement

CrystalIdea Software has created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate its firm commitment to privacy. The policy discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for our Web site, located at http://www.crystalidea.com. This policy is incorporated in, and subject to, the Terms and Conditions of Use of our Web site.

**Collecting Information:** Generally, we do not collect any personally identifiable information from individuals unless specifically provided by the individual. For example, when you request information regarding our products, promotions or warranties, you voluntarily provide your name, company, contact address, e-mail address and type of CrystalIdea Software products and supporting equipment you own or use. 

Our website uses Google Analytics, a service which transmits website traffic data to Google servers in the United States. Google Analytics does not identify individual users or associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. We use reports provided by Google Analytics to help us understand website traffic and webpage usage.

**Using Information:** Though we have the utmost respect for your privacy, any communication or material you transmit to the site by electronic mail or otherwise, is and will be treated as, nonconfidential and nonproprietary. As a general rule, we will not sell, rent, or lease your personally identifiable information and will not disclose your personally identifiable information to others except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it. We use your personal information primarily to fulfill purchases and prizes, to track compliance with our Terms and Conditions of Use, for research purposes or for marketing and promotional purposes.

**Cookies:** Google Analytics service may store 3 cookies on your PC ('_ga', '_gid' and '_gat'). In some cases the website may store 2 additional cookies ('source' and 'campaign') which track how a user came to the website (e.g. 'uninstalltool' and 'dlgabout' when a user came from the Uninstall Tool about dialog). We use this information to track purchases.

**Security:** We use industry standard efforts (such as a secure sockets or secure socket layer where appropriate) to safeguard the confidentiality of your personally identifiable information. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.

**Limits on Our Abilities** : Although your privacy is very important to us, due to the existing legal and technical environment, we cannot ensure that your personally identifiable information will not be disclosed to third parties in ways not described in this policy. For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. Additionally, we can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to private entities, law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to address or resolve inquiries or problems.

**NOTICE:** By using this site, you signify your assent to the Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our site. Your continued use of our site following the posting of changes to the policy's will mean you accept those changes. Please contact our legal department if you have any further questions or concerns regarding our Online Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions regarding the contents contained in the Online Privacy Policy, Terms and Conditions of Use, or the Copyright Statement, please contact us.
